<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Home</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Flood Risk in Houston</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/projects/cyplan101/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/projects/cyplan101/</guid>
      <description>Language: R | Program: RStudio, Carto Authors: Danielle Louie, Kobe Bilstad&#xA;Visit the GitHub profile for more details.&#xA;Abstract Link to heading As climate change increases the intensity of storms, cities must improve their urban infrastructure to adapt to severe environmental disasters. The present study investigated six factors in Houston’s urban design to understand the city’s vulnerability to flooding: precipitation patterns, storm sewer systems, pavements, land use, topography, and socioeconomic demographics.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2024 09:49:16 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/about/</guid>
      <description>About Me Link to heading Hi! I&amp;rsquo;m Danielle, a fourth-year undergraduate at UC Berkeley double-majoring in Sustainable Environmental Design and Data Science. I am passionate about utilizing technology to model and develop sustainable solutions for our environment. Throughout my student career, I have gained valuable experience in data processing and analysis, app developments and deployment, GIS mapping, 3D prototyping, sustainable research.&#xA;Active Involvement Link to heading Currently, I am a Data Scientist intern at the Eric and Wendy Schmidt Center for Data Science and Environment (DSE).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Emoji Support</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/emoji-support/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/emoji-support/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Emoji can be enabled in a Hugo project in a number of ways.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Testing Post</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/tutorial-test/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/tutorial-test/</guid>
      <description> Ideas Link to heading next and back page buttons link images and playable videos </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2D Tile-Based World Exploration Engine</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/projects/cs61b/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/projects/cs61b/</guid>
      <description>Language: Java | Program: IntelliJ | Project 3 Git Link Authors: Danielle Louie, Michelle Ngo&#xA;Overview Link to heading The objective of this project was to build an interactive &amp;ldquo;game&amp;rdquo; with randomly generated, explorable dungeon maps based on a 2D grid of tiles. You have probably come across games that use this map style, such as Pokémon, Fire Emblem, or Stardew Valley! These games typically use graphical tiles to create a more colorful and lively game experience, but for this project, my partner and I utilized text based tiles.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/contact/</guid>
      <description>Feel free to reach out through LinkedIn or email! I look forward to hearing from you!&#xA;Email: daniellelouie.07@gmail.com | danielle_louie@berkeley.edu</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
